On this enlarger, the bulb for the enlarger is located in this housing right up here.
Now, this is not just your normal light bulb that you could at your house.
It is a special photographic light bulb that you need to either order via the Internet or by at a photographic supply store.
It is very important that you get the right light.
If you get the wrong type of bulb, using a household bulb, you are going to completely ruin whatever you are working on.
So, the bulb goes in up here and it just sort of screws on over here.
One important thing about bulbs that I just learned, actually, was that a bulb will burn brighter as it is actually loosing life.
So, the filament in that bulb will actually start to burn bright, thus changing some of your enlargement times.
So, you always want to kind of keep track of how many hours you have had that bulb for, and also have a spare bulb.
Because, there is nothing worse than having a great day of printing and your bulb blows and you do not have a backup bulb.